VLADIMIR SOTIROSKI

KEY ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE AND FULL STACK DEVELOPER



PROFILE

KAE with more than 20 years' experience in the FMCG business and logistic, I decided to take new steps in my life and make my dream of coding part in my everyday life. The spark to coding started a fire. The last 2 years I spend learning almost all languages such as HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, ANGULAR JS, MySQL, PYTHON, Laravel and now Vue JS and Nuxt JS. I took few courses, and read a lot pages of coding books gathered some excellent skills for Web Developing.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Customer Service and Administration at Nelt Group

Dec 1998 - Dec 2006 Office Bitola, Macedonia

Branch Manager Assistant at Nelt Group

Jan 2007 - Mar 2014 Office and Warehouse Bitola, Macedonia

Logistic Manager at Nelt Group

Mar 2011 - Sep 2011 Office and Warehouse Luanda Angola Africa

Sales Representative at Nelt Group

Apr2014- Feb 2015 Division Food Bitola, Macedonia

Key Account Executive at Nelt Group

Feb 2015 - Present Division Procter and Gamble Bitola, Macedonia

EDUCATION

EMUC Guro Salaj - Bitola

Sep 1990 - Jun 1994 Electrician

University St Kliment Ohridski - Bitola

Oct 2014 - Present Part-time student. Final year of studies Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

COURSES

Customer training program

Apr 2013 - Sales Academy Nelt, Skopje

Python programming fundamentals

May 2019 - Academy Campster, Beograd

Full Stack Developer

Jul 2020 - Academy Javen Advertising, Bitola

Vue JS and Nuxt JS

Present - Udemy Online

Details

Partizanska 57/10 Bitola, North Macedonia, **070280907**

Vladobit@yahoo.com

Date /Place of birth

06.08.1975 Bitola

Nationality

Macedonian

Driving license

B, C, C1, E

Links

Skills

Front End Development:

Back End Development:

Design:

Corel Draw • • • • • • • Figma

Sales:

Communication Organisation Organisation Negotiation Team Work

Hobbies

Skiing Golf Swimming

Languages

Macedonian Serbian-Croatian English

native native average